When I grow up, I’ll come to save you
At that place, where you said you’d wait.
The selfish promise we made long, long ago
Last night by the cherry blossoms, you weren’t there.
Even so, I’ll continue to wait
I'll be there when you smile
While watching you smile,
I wanted to take in the blossoming cherry trees
The moonlight streaming through the full blossoms
Underneath God's cherry tree
With cut off breaths, you are
covered in wounds, covered in wounds, covered in wounds,
covered in wounds, covered in wounds...
How, how, how can this be?
All this time, it’s like
I’ve never even seen the real you.
The scattering cherry blossoms twinkled like stars
Glittering with blood, tears and fresh wounds
Your beautiful, grotesque appearance
I sought to save that fleeting expression
Yet with just a single glance
I fell in love
I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love it!
The beautiful you
completely covered head to toe in wounds
I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love it!
While gazing at your smile
I wiped away the tears with my bloody hands.
Both your heart and your body are covered in fresh wounds
While dizzily looking back at you
More than your smile, it seems as if,
as if I've discovered something even more beautiful
I'll run, I'll run, run to meet you
I'll even run to your place
Before we get there you will make that sudden turn
A world of just the two of us
A closed up world so no one can see
Right now I feel like I can do anything
Even make those noisy adults shut up
We can do, we can do it
In our closed up world
I can make you
I can make you even more beautiful
I love, I love, I love,  I love,  I love, I love it!
The beautiful you
completely covered head to toe in wounds
I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love it!
If it's me, I can give you
even more beautiful wounds
I used to cherish the memory of your smile but
I can't live like that anymore
Since I have come to know
an even more beautiful side of you
The cherry blossoms are quick to fall
Cherry blossoms before dawn
Things like the memory of your smile
Along with God's cherry tree
The fleeting beauty is sure to scatter, right?