Let’s follow the lead of the corpses and dance
The dance of the corpses
Let’s follow the lead of the corpses and dance.
possessing, possessing possessing someone...
to find a company to the afterlife.
grudges, grudges, Let's embrace the grudges
to be shared and enjoyed along the journey
This dance of the corpses,
will make your head colorful, pitter patter
It's an invitation for you who yearning to die,
to get away from the painful life
over here in sweet sweet realm of paradise
come here?
The dance of corpses
the dance of corpses
Living is such a drag
have some joy inside your heart
let your intestine rotten away
In this happy and fun dance of the corpses
you are already our companion
such massive fascination, so
Let's dance along in the graveyard
cha cha u
The dance of the corpses
along the lead of the corpses
Dancing style along the lead of the corpses
The life after death...
from time to time is...
just like that.
A punishment for your sins,
it's long and winded. Don't mind that.
just start with take one step,  one step, one step...
just like that...
come here?
The dance of the corpses
the dance of the corpses
Good luck escaping from the underworld,
the place they pour the boiling oil flowing through the creases of the brain
The dance of the corpses
the dance of the corpses
Living is such a drag
have some joy inside your heart
let your intestine rotten away
In this happy and fun dance of the corpses
you are already our companion
such massive fascination, so
Let's dance along in the graveyard
cha cha u
The dance of the corpses
In this happy and fun dance of the corpses
you are already our companion
such massive fascination, so
Let's dance along in the graveyard