On the roof of the last train,
fragments of me were forgotten
Gathered together, grilled, and eaten
You were visible from the sky
You're always the same
I never change either
Without a place, I found myself
merely wandering about the town
'Cuz I wanna spend these endless nightmares together with you
I put out the little lamp of hope holding you up
Before the cracks in my heart can be filled up by a maze,
I'll lead you away to a star
where nobody else can reach
Come along, come along,
We are being called by that far away star
It's okay, it's okay
You can say goodbye now, it's okay.
Come along, come along,
Even if you die, I will forgive you
So it's okay, it's okay,
I whisper to you
I'll accept it, accept it, all of you.
I lure you out of the valley of emotion
Return them, return them, my forgotten things
'Cuz I wanna spend these endless nightmares together with you
I light the great big lamp of despair holding you up
On the roof of the last train,
fragments of me were forgotten
Don't overlook the gloom that sinks into my eyes
Come along, come along,
Since you were seen from such a far away star
It's okay, it's okay,
'Cuz I whisper to you
Come along, come along,
Even if you die, I'll forgive you
So it's okay, it's okay
It'd really be alright.