Let's go to heaven !
Me and you bidding fun farewell
Let's go,  let's go to heaven
With no one to bother us anymore,  in the sky just for us
In quiet space without anything
You who only have a body
I give you my arms and legs
I who become only arms and legs
You give me your body
This is the heaven
Together we two are one
Spinning on a merry go round,
spun around and around
Yours for you, Mine for me  we say good bye.
Let's go to heaven
Me and you, together want to enjoy breaking apart
Let's go, Let's go to heaven
With no one to bother us anymore,  in our joyful wedding
We will do it, We will do it in heaven
Me and you together slowly bidding farewell
Your fingers, wrists, arms, and shoulders disappear,
Toes, heels, and knees disappear.
Thighs, back, stomach, chest, neck,
Face, head, everything disappear.
Me and you, are two no more
So Happy Birthday for now
Me and you light up only one candle
Let's dance around the cake
Dancing around and around, the two souls tired and disappeared
This is the heaven,
where alone is nothing
nothing is everything, it's the same
With you as you, and me as me,  because we are here somewhere
Let's go to heaven !
Me and you together are tired above the sky.
Let's go, Let's go to heaven !
Be the clouds, be the sky, be the stars, and be a dream,
Me and you together will have a joyful wedding
We will do it, We will do it in heaven !
Me and you dancing until we can't tell each other apart
We are happy, We are happy in heaven !
We may not be seen anywhere anymore, but we can be together anywhere
There is no one bother us in the sky anymore
We are happy, We are happy in heaven !
We may not be seen anywhere anymore, but we can be together anywhere
Let's dance together for the eternity