"Don't look at me in that way." [ Boku o Sonna Me de Minaid ]
Subtitles made by: Niku Shani
[ Boku o sonna me de minaide, mama. ] Don't look at me with those eyes, Mama.
[ Shinda no ga hazukashiku naru daro! ]  Or I'll be embarrassed about dying!
[ (Mama) Gunyu gunyu no hoppe ga. ]  (Mama) My milky, white cheeks.
[ Poppukoon no you ni futtonda boku o. ] Have blown away like popcorn.
[ Sonna me de minaide, papa. ] Don't look at me with those eyes, Papa.
[ Shinda no ga nasakenaku naru daro! ] Or I'll feel ashamed about dying!
[ (Papa) Mukai no pareedo wa. ]  The coming parade
[ Tamashii o pinsetto de hyoi to nuite... ] Plucked my soul out with a pair of tweezers...
[ ...Houri nagete! ] ...And threw me away!
[ Chin! ton! shan! ] Ding! Bonk! Shing!
[ shan shaba daba daba- ] Shabadabadaba-
[ Torero torero, toremoro! ]  Trill trill, goes the tremolo!
[  Lalelula toremororu lalila. ] Lalelula tremololing lalila.
[ Torotoro ni muketa, boku wa doko ni ikun daro? ] Melting with a drip-drop, I wonder where I'm going?
[ Osora o tobi koete. ] Leaping through the sky.
[ Orugooru no kushiba ni hasamaru. ] I get caught inside the teeth of a music box.
[ Kushiba no furue ga- ] The music box's-
[ -kimochi ii no de! ]  -Trembling feels good!
[ Pyu, pyu to kokizami ni boku wa hajikechau. ] And I get minced and chopped up with a pop, pop.
[ Karada ga chiisaku. ] My body becomes small.
[ Tobichitte boku wa takusan ni naru. ] And I scatter around into pieces.
[ Karappo no... ]  My empty brain...
[ ...Noumiso ga... ]   ...Melt together...
[ ...Torotoro ni torokete ohoshisama ni naru. ]     ...Into a large star.
[ Heitai no juusei wa- ] The soldier's gunshots-
[ -Nari yamanai!! ] -Won't stop!
[ Ensou wa- ] The performance-
[ -Nari yamanai! ]   -Won't end!
[ Orugooru wa... ] The Music box...
[ ...Itsumademo tomaranai. ] ...Never stops.
[ Tooi- ] The Music box-
[ -Kuni no hate de- ] -Keeps singing out-
[ -Orugooru- ] -Out to the-
[ -Wa nari tsuzukeru. ] -Far ends of the land.
[ Daijoubu minna... ] It's okay everyone...
[ ...Hoshi ni nareba nakama sa!] ...If we become stars we'll all get along!
[ Niji no you ni hikaru. ] Shining like a rainbow.
[ Tamashii no saigo wa. ]  The final moment of my soul.
[ Purun to gumi no you ni.] Like pudding and gummy candy.
[ Kudakete tokete kieru... ] Shatters and melts into nothingness...
[ ...Dakara... ] ...So...
[ Boku o sonna me de minaide, mama. ] Don't look at me with those eyes, Mama
[ Shinda no ga hazukashiku naru daro... ] Or I'll be embarrassed about dying...
[ (Mama) Kawaii jibun o- ] (Mama) The cute little me-
[ Kimochi yosa ni makete sutechatta boku o. ] Who gave into the good feelings and threw myself away.
[ Sonna me de minaide, papa. ] Don't look at me with those eyes, Papa.
[ Shinda toko minaide okure yo! ] Look away from the place where I died!
[ (Papa) Datte shinu no- ] (Papa) Because I'm ashamed-
[-Kimochi yokatta boku wa hazukashiku tte...] -For having felt so good while dying...
[ Jan, Janpa! Jan, Janpa! Shan-Shanpara! ] Clang, clang, pop! Clang, clang, pop! Shing, shing, clatter!
[ Dorori tororu. ] Drip Drip Drop.
[ Torero torero, toremoro. ] Trill trill, goes the tremolo.
[ Lalelula- ] Laleluna-
[ -Toremororu lalila. ] -Tremoloing lalila.
[ Shiroku torotoro ni parapara harararara... ] Melting into white and drip drip dropping away...
[ Ohiru no... ] That afternoon...
[ ...Kaerimichi... ] ...On my way home...
[ ...Jitensha de kudari michi kudaru kudaru. ] ...I rode down, down, down the big hill.
[ Hojorin tsukete... ] With my training wheels on...
[ ...Semai ouchi no... ] ...I passed through...
[ ...Semai sukima no aida o nukete. ] ...The narrows cracks in the narrow roads.
[ Hajimete... ] For the first time...
[ ...Kaze ni naru... ] ...I became the wind...
[ ...Oku no kokoro wa kaze ni kowasareru. ] ...And my heart was broken by the wind.
[ Konna ni... ] It felt...
[ ...kimochi ii nante... ] ...So good...
[ ...Boku ga kaze ni kowasareteku no wa. ] ...Being shattered by the wind like that.
[ Itsumademo- ] Always going-
[ -Kudaru Kudaru! ] -Down and Down!
[ Owara- ] That slope-
[ -Nai sakamichi! ] -Without an end!
[ Hito no sugata wa... ] Without a single trance...
[ ...Doko ni mo mitsukerenai. ] [ ...Of another person. ]
[ Le wa- ] The houses-
[ -Shoumetsu shite. ] -Disappear.
[ Densen wa- ] The power lines-
[ -Yugami kuneru. ] [ -Bend and sway. ]
[ Kaze ni kezurarete... ] Cut down by the wind...
[ ...Karada ga akaku tokeru. ] ...My body dissolves into red.
[ Soshite boku wa kieru... ] And then I was gone...
[ ...Tamashii o nokoshita mama... ] ...With just my soul remaining...
[ Aru wa hazu no nai jitensha to issho ni. ] Along with my bicycle that never should have existed.
[ Itsumademo... ] Always...
[ ...doko made mo... ] ...And forever... ]
[ Boku o sonna me de minaide, mama. ] Don't look at me with those eyes, Mama.
[ Boku wa mou doko ni mo inain dakara! ] Because I'm no longer anywhere!
[ (Mama) Mama wa mini kaa ya manga o ippai katte kureta yo ne. ] (Mama) Mama bought me so many toy cars and comic books.
[ Sonna me de minaide papa. ] Don't look at me with those eyes, Papa.
[ Boku wa kieru no ga kimochi yokattan da! ] It felt so good to disappear!
[ (Papa) Papa wa orugooru ya omocha no heitai o tsukutte kureta kedo. ] (Papa) Even though Papa made me a music box and toy soldiers.
[ Boku wa mou doko ni mo inai. ] I'm no longer anywhere.
[ Boku no tamashii wa yume no sekai e kieta! ] My soul disappeared into the world of dreams!
[ (Mama) Mama no ippai no omocha mo issho ni naka yoku tokete kietan da ne. ] (Mama) All of Mama's toys happily melted together into nothingness.
[ Boku wa mou doko ni mo inai. ] I'm no longer anywhere.
[ Mata yume de au made, sayounara! ] Until we meet again in our dreams, farewell!
[ (Papa) Papa no heitaisan wa orugooru no sukima kara te futte ita. ] (Papa) Papa's toy soldiers are waving from under the lid of the music box.
[ Pa pa pa pa pa, para-para. ] Pa pa pa pa pa, clatter.
[ Ma ma ma ma ma, bara-bararararara. ] Ma ma ma ma ma, clattererer.
[ Lalulelo lulilelo lalulo. ] Lalulelo lulilelo lalelo.