You're a useless, useless, useless child
The most useless child in entire world
You are useless child
Song by : Kikuo
Study, exercise, speaking, you can't do anything
You're a poor and dull dirty brat
You can't even say your own name, yet I still love you
drooling, booger, dandruf, and piss
I do not mind it cry-baby, don't mind, don't mind
Come here, let me protect you
together, together, together with me
La la,  Lullaby for good night
What song do you want to sing together,
Let's sing it,  Let's sing it together with me,...
oh lonely child, child
You're a useless, useless, useless child
The most useless child in entire world
If it were not for me, you would be dead child
You're a useless, useless, useless child
sad, sad, and good for nothing
I will be the one who help you
Monster, Ghost, Insignificant human,
Urinal ornament, rejected from school
A loud voice from the dry mouth.
Let’s listen to scream of a stick.
Nevertheless time goes on and on
You don't have enough brain nor time, child
It’s too late,  you’re mentally retarded
Oh sweet child, good child of mine
La la,  Lullaby for good night
Let's sleep tight with me
Dance, Dance, Always dancing oh lonely...
child, child, child, child
You're a useless, useless, useless child
The most useless child in entire world
You are lonely, lonely, lonely child
I will protect you forever
But I can't keep the child with me
child ran away from my side
Without consider all the wounds
Still it was just what happen
child, child child, child
I’m a useless, useless, useless child
There is no useless child anymore
No body help me anymore
I'm lonely, lonely, lonely child
There is no lonely child anymore
If only I can turn back the time