Why is it so fun to destroy things? Olé!
Translation: Releska
Since I became aware, I’ve destroyed a whole bunch of things:
Clocks, teacups, remote controls, building blocks…
Important and precious things are particularly entertaining:
Dolls, puzzles, phones, photos…
Whether they got mad or cried, everyone looked so scared. Still…
Things are so easy to break, and they’ve taken such good care of them
yet they leave them in arm’s reach.
I get all weird and find the tension so fun. Silently, I reach out.
pitter-patter, pitter-patter, pitter-patter, pitter-patter
It’s especially fun to break your things.
pitter-patter, pitter-patter, pitter-patter
Your valuables are even more fun to break.
Things are all in pieces.
Close, open…
I can’t have fun if it’s just once
so I fix it, break it, fix it, and break it again.
You, too, forget what it originally looked like.
I’ve even demolished things crammed full of memories:
Stuffed toys, plastic models, pianos, letters…
I’ve even carefully demolished things full of feelings:
Musical instruments, paintings, pottery, sculptures…
When people put their hopes and feelings in things,
Their souls cross over and dwell in them, since they’ll last forever.
The more precious things exist, the more souls there are.
They breathe fragilely, enjoy life, and are then silently killed.
pitter-patter, pitter-patter, pitter-patter, pitter-patter
I want to keep breaking your soul.
pitter-patter, pitter-patter, pitter-patter,
I want to erase your living soul.
In pieces, in pieces,
things end up in pieces
and the moment your soul vanishes…
I’ll fix it, I’ll break it
I’ll fix it and break it.
I laugh and you cry.
la, la, la, la...
Still,
pitter-patter, pitter-patter, pitter-patter
You followed along. You love me.
I love you, who also loves me.
pitter-patter, pitter-patter, pitter-patter
Your soul is possessing me now.
My soul is possessing you now.
pitter-patter, pitter-patter, pitter-patter
I crumble up your precious thing.
It feels so good the moment it vanishes.
pitter-patter, pitter-patter
I destroyed myself, so precious to you,
So I fix it and break it and then
I can’t fix it. I can never
say sorry to you.
movie by redegg
illustration by temi
music &amp; lyric by kikuo