I’ve existed on this seashore but
The real me descended from above
Hate the light shining this place
This body is familiar to the night
Disappearing, disappearing, transparent, transparent
Darkness flying with leisure
Looking to the starry sky
Where it doesn’t compete the open sea
Now, nothing’s here
The sun rises, rises, rises, rises
My own existence
Can’t be seen here
The sun rises, rises, rises, rises
This place where my breaths are leaving
Nothing but fragments of my existence
It doesn’t feel good (it doesn’t feel good)
It doesn’t feel good
I’m hearing everything, but no one is here
Today’s firstborn will leave, feathers intact
As this gap should be dark as night
I’m enamored by the morning sun to no avail
The sun is shining, shining, shining, shining
My own blood
Can’t be seen here
The sun is shining, shining, shining, shining
This place where I’m exchanging
Glances to the light; my jumbled thoughts
Doesn’t feel good (it doesn’t feel good)
Doesn’t feel good
The sun rises, rises, rises, rises
My own existence
Can’t be seen here
The sun rises, rises, rises, rises
This place where my breaths are leaving
Nothing but fragments of my existence
It doesn’t feel good (it doesn’t feel good)
It doesn’t feel good