Inside of the snow,
melting, melting, disappearing,
Midwinter's daughter, we will embrace, will embrace,
embrace forever
Dance with me, thump, thump, thump
No way, no way la la la
I really hate to dance
I am disliked by you
And so we'll dance, but we'll dance poorly
In the short springtime, we'll be merry
Cheerfully, you accepted
Winter in the nude
a lifeless and chill wind
makes the single dead tree lonely
suck it in until you're tired
play until you're tired
oh wanting dancer
Inside of the snow,
Melting, melting, disappearing
Like the shriveled up tree,
I'll embrace you
the frost is sure to come
to chill, to chill, and freeze us over
Midwinter's daughter;
we will embrace, will embrace, embrace forever
The warmth that greeted my naked body
I clung onto that frozen body
You can no longer escape,
Accepting every last bit of me
Dance with me, thump, thump, thump
Okay, okay la la la
You are once again
about to recieve spring
in the midst of my warmth
Over time, over time,
let's go
Inside of the snow
Melting, melting, becoming nothing
I held onto
your dead and withered body
The frost is sure to come
forever, forever, staying frozen
If it's midwinter's daughter,
we will embrace, will embrace, embrace to the end