Come, come here crow
Into the pitch black darkness
I’ll give you candy that can’t melt away
So give me your wings and feet, ok?
I’ll give you a balloon that cannot break
Let’s have fun blowing it up forever
Come, come here crow
Into the pitch black swirl
I’ll give you a lung that cannot drown
So give me your memories of the sky
So, dance with a body that can no longer fly
Until it echoes with only dried bones
Come, I’ll grant you an eternity
Until you become a doll wandering in a dream
Stars that don’t disappear
A sun that doesn’t go down
Let’s enjoy it together
Let’s finish this game
Until you wither up
Give me your soul please
So, dance with a body that can no longer fly
Until it echoes with only dried bones
Come, I’ll grant you an eternity
Until I completely drink your body dry
Let’s end this dance
Until you rot away
Let’s enjoy it together