In a night filled with difficulty,  I become a wolf
The moon's day is being filled up with the blood's unceasing noise; I can't wait
A bear is just a face with tears,
And seven colors are glaring, dancing, at the starry sky and hollering
In a night filled with difficulty, I become a wolf
Tonight, bathe in the blood at the party slipping and sliding about.
As I keep getting hurt, I can't protect it
Burn it until it's ruined; then serve it
The black blood overfills in my chest, as like drowning in the tide.
With our backs facing the full moon, let's invite them in
To the best, it is so good; that fleeting feeling..
The body is rotting away from under the domination from that beast
The fakes boredom makes it so the people can not return to their own world.
In a night filled with difficulty, I become a wolf
I rejoice many times as the unseen end of the party draws near
As I keep getting hurt, I can't protect it
My starved blood is being reflected in their eyes, in their eyes.
Ooh, Aah!
La la la la, la la la la, la la la la la la la la