And so you became the moon
(sky) while I became a star in the universe
Beside the Milky Way
We'll always be together!
And then I crumbled and fell apart
And the moon fell into the open hole
We'll be together forever
even at the very bottom of the universe!
Moon
And so you became the Moon
And so you became the
She's swaying
I put the moon's head into my pocket
The dead moon's night sky is
Darkly   darkly
Falling down
Spinning   spinning   the maddened Yukionna is dancing
with frozen eyes I --
d r i p with frozen eyes I --
d r o p d r o p with frozen eyes I --
with frozen eyes I --
The collapsed body fell from the sky  with frozen eyes I --
The collapsed body fell from the sky
And so I became a star
And you became the moon in the universe
Next to the aurora lights
We'll always be together!
And then I fell down and disappeared
on to the opposite side of the Yukionna
While looking at moon from the very bottom of Naraku on to the opposite side of the Yukionna
While looking at moon from the very bottom of Naraku
I can't hear anything
I can't touch anything I can't hear anything
I can't touch anything
I can't move
But I can still see
Inside the warm pocket that I was placed into But I can still see
Inside the warm pocket that I was placed into
Spinning spinning     the painful trembling is kindly
letting me sleep comfortably
d r i p letting me sleep comfortably
d r i p
d r o p d r i p
d r o p
In the night sky I bid farewell to the broken you
And so you became the moon
The gloomy and broken me
the broken lump keeps shining
And so I became a star
The moon won't shine anymore
The star is also disappearing
Into the light
And so both the moon and the star disappear
The disappeared couple cannot be found anywhere
At the very bottom of the universe
they are together forever!
And so the moon and star disappear
That is a bedtime fairytale
At the very bottom they are together forever!