The god of death reflected on the evening sea
It catches my dissolving heart
I feel good
I slowly made up my mind
Here, the tender darkness averts
its eyes to death,
and embraces me
Hey, world's kindest god of death
Take good care of me tonight
Melting away, melting away, melting away
The last night
Disappearing, disappearing
Within the greatest pleasure
The paradise illuminated by a rainbow lantern
Lifts up my dying body
gently
It whispers quietly
Now and that time,
Feathers hold me softly
and release
Hey, world's kindest god of death
Where are you taking me?
Melting away, melting away, melting away
The last heart
Disappearing, disappearing
Within the greatest pleasure
Falling away, falling away, falling away
gently and lightly
Soaring off, soaring off
toward the greatest pleasure