Translation by Achamo
If I go to hell I'll be saved,
if I rise up to heaven we can meet again.
I love you, begging
to be constricted, in comfort, in comfort
A Happy Death
"More, more. Strangle me harder."
Gasping in a child-like voice:
"I love you."
In a weak voice:
"Goodbye."
"Thank you," you whispered, and then died.
If I fall to hell I'll be saved,
if I rise up to heaven we can meet again.
Please give me my punishment in hell.
You're in heaven, pure.
If that world's nothingness, let's go there.
I want to see you. Can I?
Now, for me, a blissful death
I want to, I want to die like this.
I love you, able to answer so honestly and purely.
In a happy-sounding voice "Is this okay?"
"Does it feel good?" I whispered, and killed you.
If I fall to hell I'll be saved,
if I rise up to heaven we can meet again.
Please give me my punishment in hell.
You'll go to heaven, pure.
If my sins are cleared, let's meet there.
Come, come.
A blissful death to you as well.