You've always laughed at me, ridiculed me and made me suffer
Ah, ah, you're gonna find this so fun
Tonight, tonight, a secret revenge plan
It's my...
TURN NOW!
(Reincarnation Ascension)
Music : Kikuo / Artwork : si_ku
Reincarnate, ascend - until end up as another being
Reincarnate, combine - keep regenerating...
The dawn is fast approaching, take the string and undo the knot
Next nightfall there won't be anything left, we'll both be something more
Keep the string tight, so we can stay apart for now
Hah...
As I stop breathing, I'm having so much fun
A curse, a curse: with a forbidden spell of rebirth,
Resurrect, resurrect, just like usual...
Reincarnate, ascend - until end up as another being
Reincarnate, combine - keep regenerating...
Reincarnate, ascend - until we both become monstrosity,
Reincarnate, combine - decay and regenerate...
Ah...
Keep doing the forbidden spell,
until turning into monstrosity...
Reincarnate, ascend - *unfathomable gibberish*
Reincarnate, combine - *unfathomable gibberish*
Reincarnate, ascend - until we both become monstrosity
Reincarnate, combine - decay and regenerate...
Reincarnate, ascend - *unfathomable gibberish*
Reincarnate, combine - *unfathomable gibberish*