Translation: Hazuki no Yume CC by: A Kindly Anon
Ah...
Please, wake up - wake up from my nightmare
I cannot breathe
In this world
Please, I beg you
Please let me wake
I'm waiting for help
Forever
O Light - Kikuo Singer: Hanatan
On this dark, dark night
With these legs that can't carry me further
I'm waiting for dawn
Utterly still
Please, wake up
Please wake up from my nightmare
In this world
Full of illusions
Where, where am I supposed to be?
Here I am, wandering around
Forever
Where am I to be? (To be?)
There are so many reasons
I cannot be here
I'm being hung upside down in the air
Ah, someone wake me up!
Please, wake up
Please wake from my nightmare
I can't breathe
in this world
Please, somehow bring us to one another
For I believe there is salvation waiting for me
Please wake up!
Wake from this nightmare
On this planet, I cannot use my voice
Where, where am I supposed to go?
I'm yearning for you
In utter stillness
Forever
Forever...
O Light HIKARI YO