He opens my ribs and drinks my soup
With a personal kiss from my stomach
I don't think I have any taste
But if it makes Papa happy...
Suck up my yellow fat with a straw  Stick it into my pee-pee and suck it up like that too
Fill it up with my poop and bake it  Even though my body is collapsing for Papa's sake
I'm sorry, after all, I don't have a good feeling
A big brother I don't know told me, ahh
Even though my collapsed body is pitiful, he kindly reaches out a hand
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I must be a bad girl
So forgive me, forgive me, poor little me
I'm sorry, goodbye, I'm a bad girl for running away from Papa
I'm sorry, forgive me for falling in love with someone who's not Papa
Big Brother gulps down my amniotic fluid. He breaks open my hard stomach and touches the inside
Without eating me, he treats me gently  Even though my collapsed body is ugly
I'm sorry, that's not a good feeling I have
Big Brother must hate me, ahh
My collapsed body gives a bad feeling  It can be kept on file, and it's the end
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I must be a bad girl
So forgive me, forgive me, lonely little me
I'm sorry, goodbye, I'm a bad girl for returning to Papa
I'm sorry, forgive me for not being able to love my cruel Papa
When he came home, Papa was with a lot of people
They said they had believed I'd return
They want to eat my collapsed body until the end  That's what they said
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I must be a bad girl
So forgive me, forgive me, poor little me
I'm sorry, is it tasty? That's the taste of a warm heart
I'm sorry, even though it hurts, my heart is satisfied
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I must be a bad girl
So forgive me, forgive me, lonely little me
I'm sorry, even though it hurts, as long as you eat me and it tastes good,
I'm happy, goodbye, everybody eat up except for my heart