Our ending is the ending of the world
The ending of the world is the ending of everyone
Your very onset will take someone else's place
Someone else's ending will be our place to take
*chuckle* *chuckle* *chuckle* *chuckle*
The cursed paper-doll bearing our name has gone
Inside the fairy-like dancing flame, a lonely person turns into dust
Here we go!
Dusty Dusty Dusty Dusty
Reduced to dust and fly away
Crackle Crackle Crackle Crackle
Turn to ashes and fly away
Dusty Dusty Dusty Dusty
Scorching and soaring
Crackle Crackle Crackle Crackle
See who will be the last one standing?
Our ending is the ending of the world
The ending of the world is the ending of everyone
Your very onset will take someone else's place
Someone else's ending will be our place to take
Your pathetic self that nobody knows is now locked inside a box where you'll unable to see the dawn
Wrapped under the light of dancing moonlight, in your last final glance...
who do you see?
Here we go!
Dusty Dusty Dusty Dusty
Reduced to dust and disappear
Crackle Crackle Crackle Crackle
Turn into fine powder and fly away
Dusty Dusty Dusty Dusty
Scorching and soaring
Crackle Crackle Crackle Crackle
See who will be the last one standing?
*chuckle* *chuckle* *chuckle* *chuckle*