translation by Sunny Subs
And so you became the moon while  I became a star in the universe
By the bank of the Milky Way, we'll always be together!
And then I crumbled and fell apart  and the moon fell into the open hole
We'll be together forever even at  the very bottom of the universe! hyuu hyuu hyuu uu
And then you Became the Moon
She's swaying, I put the moon's head into my pocket
The dead moon's night sky is darkly darkly falling down
Spinning spinning the maddened Yukionna is dancing
With frozen eyes I -- d r i p
The collapsed body fell from the sky  with frozen eyes I -- d r i p
d r i p d r i p d r o p d r o p d r o p d r o p
And so I became a star and  you became the moon in the universe
Next to the aurora lights, we'll always be together!
While looking at moon from the very bottom of  Naraku on to the opposite side of the Yukionna
While looking at moon from the very bottom of Naraku
La la la...
I can't hear anything, I can't touch anything,  I can't move but I can still see
Inside the warm pocket that I was placed into
Spinning spinning the painful trembling is kindly
Letting me sleep comfortably d r i p
In the night sky I bid farewell to the broken you  d r o p d r i p
d r i p d r o p d r i p d r o p
And so you became the moon,  the gloomy and broken me
The broken lump keeps shining
And so I became a star, the moon won't shine anymore
The star is also disappearing into the light
And so both the moon and the star disappear,  the disappeared couple cannot be found anywhere
At the very bottom of the universe,  they are together forever!
And so the moon and star disappear,  that is a bedtime fairytale
At the very bottom they are together forever!